buzzerhut.com 2018-12-26

# Buzzerhut: Webs Largest Blogs & Website Submission+Search Directory | Submit your blog

In general, you can visit our site without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself.  

Your privacy is important to Buzzerhut and Focus Infosoft. We believe it is important for you to know how we treat the information we receive from you, on the Internet.

The personal information collected on this site will be used to operate the site and to provide the service or carry out the transactions you have requested. We may use personal information to provide you with more effective customer service to improve the site and to make the site easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information or by customizing the site to your particular preference or interest.  

We use personal information provided by you to develop our marketing strategy, improve our website and enhance our services.

The personal information we collect may include your name, title, company or organization name, work e-mail, work phone, work or home address, information about your job function and information about your company.  

In connection with a job application or inquiry on the website you may provide us with information about yourself, such as a resume or curriculum vitae. We may use this information throughout Focus and its related entities for the purpose of employment consideration or your inquiry, except where you tell us or not to, we will keep the information for future consideration.

We may amend this privacy policy at any time in our discretion without any prior notice. You periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect.
